So here we will be talking about the type B communication.
It will be short as in fact there is no much difference between type B and type A only in some certain
commands.
In fact, the type B communication is much more shorter than the type A communication.
So in type B, the first command same thing as the type A is is request B.
This is the first command to be sent during the communication.
The B command is sent by the reader to generate the field for the card that supports the type B communication.
So it's almost the same thing as a type as the type A communication.
When we will send a request a but here we will be we will have more bytes.
So the answer to the request B will be an atcb answer to request b.
So as you can see here, we will have more bytes than the Atca.
In fact, this is the first answer to be sent by the car to the reader in a type B communication.
All the cards in the idle state will respond with 80 KB to the Recv command from the Atcb.
We can retrieve the bit rate supported by the card.
Also, if the card supports different bit rates for each direction or not.
If the card is compliant with ISO 14,443 four or not, and also the PW pie.
In fact, in the type A communication we can extract extract the bit rate supported by the card through
the ATS, which is the forced response.
However, in type B communication we can extract this information through the first response by the
card, which is the answer to request b Atcb.
Then the reader will send the Attrib command.
This Attrib command will select a single card from from the field.
It will also send the bit rate that will continue the communication with.
In a type A, we select the bit rate for the communication in the PES.
However, in the in the type B communication, it will be done in the second command sent by the reader,
which is the Attrib command.
Then the response to the Attrib command will be the Attrib response.
In fact, this is the answer that the Cod sends to the Attrib command.
Same thing as the for type A from the request A to the response.
All the communication will be done in 106kbps, which is FC divided 128.
However, in type B, all these five first command in type A will be commanded will be converted only
to two commands.
Request B and Attrib command and the answer will be 80 KB and Attrib response.
Same thing.
Request B Atcb Attrib command and Attrib response will be done at only at 106kbps.
And then we will start exchanging the information.
We will start sending I blocks, R blocks, S blocks.
Same exact same thing as the type A communication.